[Music]
Life is harder than i like to think
But it's easy when you're by my side
No point in calling you'll just have to see
The fundamentals of our life tonight
Cause I've been looking at a photograph of you
And I've been thinking about all the ways you move
This isolation got me feeling like a move my love
Yeah when I wake up I feel empty not beside you
My whole life been searching just to find you
This quarantine it hasn't got the right to keep us apart.
Did you say something?
No riding your skateboard in the hallway.
This is the last time I'm going to tell you Sleet.
Yeah, yeah. You got it Mr Wilson.
You're late again Sleet, next time it's a write up.
Thanks for the heads up teach.
William, get out of my seat.
Your seat? Ahaha, last I checked it didn't belong to you anymore snot bag.
What?
Today is the first day of the second semester.
So I let the students choose where they want to sit for the rest of the year.
One of the perks of getting here on time.
But this is my seat, and the best seat in the class.
It's the one closest to the pencil sharpener.
Correction. It was your seat once faggot, but it's mine now.
Okay, well where am I supposed to sit?
There aren't any more open seats.
Actually, there's one far in the back. Right over there.
Teacher you can't do this to me, I can't sit over there.
Why not?
Because that's, that's Dingo
Everybody hates Dingo. He always smells like Bush's baked beans.
And he pooped his pants during social studies last week.
He always stands by the vending machine, to try and steal people's candy bars.
Hey James, you want a fucking candy bar?
Yes, I could go for a snickers.
Sorry, did you say you wanted a snickers or a milky way?
Give me that bitch!
Let go, this is mine!
I'll fucking rape you bitch!
[Screaming]
If I have to sit next to Dingo I'll be a laughingstock for the rest of the year.
You should have thoughts about that before coming to class late.
Now go take your seat before I write you up.
Hi, what's your name? My name is Dingo.
I'm sorry you had your seat stolen from you.
But you really should have gotten here earlier if you wanted to keep it.
Don't talk to me until lunch.
Are you a planetary exchange student too?
You look different from the other students.
Are you also from Mobius?
I heard a lot of other Mobians signed up for the planetary exchange student program to come to Earth.
But I never dreamed any of them would have also chosen to come to this school.
That's so cool. Hey, can you teach me how to skateboard?
Can you skate anywhere you want on that fine piece of ass?
Like McDonald's or to the store to buy a can of Bush's baked beans?
Has anybody ever told you you got a fat fucking dumptruck ass?
I mean shit, bitch. You could fit a lawnmower in that thing.
Why are you still talking to me?
You said I could talk to you after lunch.
I did? Did I really say that? I don't think so.
Hey, William... Why's Sleet still hanging out with Dingo?
I don't know, but watch this Oliver.
Damn, William. First you steal his seat in math class, now you're going to break his stupid long nose.
You're crazy today. I haven't seen you like this since you tried to rape the PE teacher.
It almost makes me want to kiss you... and I would if you would let me... Just kidding I'm not gay.
Mr Wilson had it coming.
Just like Sleet. Sleet's a Mobian, and Mobian's have no place on Earth.
William... Are you racist?
It's just basic nature. The weak should always fear the strong.
And I am the strongest man in school.
I never told anyone this Oliver,
So you have to keep it a secret.
But I'm not really a 16 year old boy like the rest of you.
I'm actually a 36 year old man.
Hiyah!
What the fuck was that?
Watch where you're throwing this thing bitch!
You could have seriously hurt my best friend.
[Music]
[Farting]
Shit! I think I just pooped my fucking pants!
What are you waiting for fool?
Take me to the bathroom.
Oh hey William. What do you want?
I thought you always poop at exactly 5am.
Isn't it only two in the afternoon right now?
Wait, I thought you always poop alone.
What's going on here?
Me and my buddy Oliver here saw that you became quick friends with Dingo.
Dingo's not my friend. I just have to sit next to him during class now. That's all.
But you were eating together at lunch.
And he saved you from being knocked out by that ball during gym class.
He's the one following me around. I've been trying to get him off my back all day.
Why does Oliver there have a baseball bat?
Don't you get it now Sleet?
You used to be one of the cool kids like us.
But since you started hanging out with Dingo, that title of yours is gone.
You're pretty much on the level of a bitch now.
What? No, I'm still one of the cool kids.
I'm way cooler than you are William.
And how the fuck is Oliver a cool kid?
He just moved here from France two days ago.
And he pooped his pants in social studies on his first day.
Yeah... And that's what makes me cool... Bitch.
Are you really going to make me ask where this clown came from?
There's no way he goes to this school.
He's got to be 30 years old at least.
This is my older brother Dominic, or as he likes to be called: Doodoo the clown.
I call myself Doodoo because after I kill someone, I take a massive fucking doodoo in their mouth.
During the day he works during the day he works as a teacher's assistant over at the elementary school.
But at night he's an assassin who hunts down and kills anybody I want gone.
He was nice enough to come out during the day, though just for this occasion.
You should be honored.
Yeah bitch.
Okay, but why is he dressed like a clown?
Is it some weird fetish shit?
Yes...
I really need to get back to class.
I think I hear the teacher calling for me.
Aaahh!
What's the rush cutie? Don't you wanna have a little fun?
Don't forget to break his legs big bro, that way he can't run away.
And Oliver, go pull down has fucking pants. I want to enjoy this.
With pleasure.
Get away!
You son of a bitch! I was going to go easy on you! You're going to regret that!
Saved by the bell. You are lucky i have a math test to get to.
This isn't over Sleet. We'll be meeting you after school.
And make sure to bring that faggot Dingo with you so we can make this quick.
Come on boys, let's make like a bunch of bananas and peel out.
Sleet, how was your pee break you didn't miss the toilet did you?
I do that a lot too.
Don't talk to me.
Shit, what am I gonna do? William is a black belt in karate.
There's no way I can fight him.
Especially if Oliver and his big brother Doodoo are also going to be there.
But I can't just back out from a fight, then I really will be a total bitch.
I won't be the coolest kid in school anymore either.
Sleet, can i tell you something?
I just said don't talk to me.
But it's important.
Fine, what is it?
Promise not to laugh.
I can't promise that.
I just wanted to say thank you for being my first friend.
What?
You know the two of us are different from everyone else in school.
Everybody here are earthlings, so they find us to be a little weird.
I've been here for half a year already, and in that time I never made a single friend.
I was beginning to think it would never happen, but then one day you showed up.
I think I was really lucky.
Oh yeah. That's pretty cool I guess.
Do you want to hang out at my place after school?
Um, actually Dingo I think I hear the teacher calling my name. You can go without me.
You got it sugar tits. Don't keep me waiting too long.
Come here you big fuck!
Those guys have got to be gone by now.
Why are you still here?
I was waiting for you to be finished. Did you do what the teacher wanted?
Are you ready to go home?
This is my first time visiting another person's house on Earth.
Although Dingo is another Mobian like me, so I guess it doesn't really count.
Have you taken an interest in my beanie baby collection?
What the hell are you wearing all of a sudden?
Whatever do you mean?
I told you I was going to slip into something more comfortable.
No you didn't, you told me you were going to take a shit.
Are you thirsty Sleet?
Not really.
Dingo put that away. We're not old enough to drink.
Ha ha, that's right. Sometimes I forget.
How can you forget your own age?
Tell me, wolf boy. Do you listen to music?
That's a pretty retarded question.
Everybody listens to music.
How about i put some on then?
Only if it's Linkin Park or Green Day.
I got you some Linkin Park right here big boy.
Fuck! Aaah! Well this really tickles my balls now I gotta go clean this up.
Don't go anywhere Sleet.
Sleet? Sleet? Where'd you go?
Hey Jimmy, what do you want?
Hey Sleet, can I ask you something?
Uh sure, I guess.
So like is it, is it, true? The rumor going around school?
What rumor?
Oh just... Well, you know.
Jimmy, I very clearly don't know what you're talking about, so just tell me.
So is it true? Is Dingo really fucking you in the ass?
What the hell have you been telling people?
You knocked down my Yu-Gi-Oh cards.
Answer me right now. Have you been telling people you fucked me?
Would that be a problem Bitch?
Get out of your seat you coward. We're going to fight.
God, this is just horrible. I haven't been this mad since you knocked over my milk at lunch.
Sorry.
Don't worry about it.
I don't understand. Why would you want to fight me?
Aren't I your best friend?
What? Like hell I'm your best friend. I'm not even your friend.
I barely know you.
You know what, saying stuff like that to me I don't think i want to be your friend anymore.
Did you, did you not listen to a word i said?
I literally just said we were never friends.
Shut up bitch!
I'm not your friend anymore. Don't talk to me.
Stupid faggot bitch. I wasted 165 bucks on that bottle of wine.
And you didn't even drink it bitch.
Look, Sleet and Dingo are fighting!
You really hit me.
Good job Sleet. You really showed him who's boss.
Yeah, that was awesome seeing him run away like a crybaby. You're the man.
Dingo?
You guys again? What have I ever done to you? Let me go, please.
Shut that hole under your fucking nose.
We're just getting started here.
[Crying]
Get away from him.
What the shit?!
I said get away from my fucking bitch!
Stay back! I, I'm not afraid of you.
That's fine. I'm not the one you should be afraid of.
Huh?
Please have mercy on me.
Silly little boy.
To give mercy is to be weak, and I am not weak.
No!
Just so you know, I would have been just fine, even if you hadn't shown up.
What are you watching?
Same thing I watch every Friday Dingo. Showdown with Bobby Flay on the Food Network.
I made you a grilled cheese.
This just in. The judge has officially stated that the three-year-old baby who shot up a school last week, may have actually been justified.
In the attack, it looks like Bartleby Montclair of Dresden will not receive any jail time.
Much to the despair of the dead children's parents.
Our reporter franklin is live just outside the courthouse.
Mr Bartleby is it true? Did you really shoot up the school and kill your fellow students?
You're damn right I did, and I'd do it again.
Don't you have any remorse for what you did? You took those children's lives.
No, you tell me bitch. Get these cameras out of my
Holy shit!
Good evening citizens of planet Mobius.
It is I, your proud and chubby little boy, your ruler the evil Doctor Robotnik.
Yes, kneel before my glory and sexiness.
This fucking sucks. Ever since this Robotnik guy has become the ruler of Mobius
He's been hijacking the airwaves every 30 minutes.
We can't watch anything.
Today my bitches, I am here to make a special announcement and shit.
I have thought long and hard about this.
Due to how great and powerful I have recently become it has come to my attention that I will need protection.
That is to say I am looking for personal bodyguards.
Did he just say bodyguards?
Don't even think about it Dingo we're bounty hunters, not bodyguards.
To be a bodyguard is basically to be somebody's bitch.
Although, I bet it would pay pretty good.
What the hell is taking you so long? Put this stupid picture up already.
It can't be that difficult.
But sir, isn't the picture kind of gay?
Nonsense, it's a cool picture.
Just for saying that i'm going to roboticize you.
Uh. This is why I only work with robots.
As you can see this fine specimen of a man would be my ideal bodyguard.
Those muscles, and beautiful hair, and I want two buddy guards
Not just one, two. So that they can each slap one of my butt cheeks.
I mean stand on either side of me if I were to ever be in danger.
Nothing would please me more than standing between two muscular men
With their massive fucking hairy balls in my face.
Men who will fight and die for me.
Let me repeat that one more time so I can make sure everybody understands the job listing.
Nothing would please me more than standing between two muscular men
With their massive fucking hairy balls in my face.
I will now repeat what I just said for the third and final time
Nothing would please me more than standing between two muscular men
With their massive fucking hairy balls in my face.
Is this really about bodyguards? This sounds more like a job listing for a gay porno.
Dingo, I think we've got a new job!